Indiana University President's Office records, 1962-1968 C304
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1962-1968
  - Dean of Students, 1962-1968; (9 folders) (Box 52)
  - DeBard, Robert L., 1967-1968 (Box 52)
  - Dee, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 52)
  - Degrees, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 52)
    - Examination for doctor of philosophy, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 52)
    - Examination for doctor degrees, miscellaneous, undated (Box 52)
    - Examination for doctor of philosophy, July 1964–June 1965 (Box 52)
    - Examination for doctor degrees, miscellaneous, undated (Box 52)
    - Examination for Doctor of Philosophy, July 1963-June 1964 (Box 53)
  - Di, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 53)
  - Discrimination, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 53)
  - Degrees (Box 53)
    - Examination for Doctor of Philosophy, June 1962-May 1963 (Box 53)
    - Examination for Doctor Degrees, miscellaneous, July 1962-March 1963 (Box 53)
  - Del, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 53)
  - Delta Sigma Rho, 1965 (Box 53)
  - Den, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 53)
  - Dental prophylaxis, Topical fluoride application (brush-in), 1966-1968 (Box 53)
  - Dentistry, February-September 1964 (Box 53)
  - Dentistry, School of (Box 53)
    - Annual report, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 53)
    - Department Chairman Meeting, 1962-1963 (Box 53)
    - Preventative Dentistry Research Institute (brush-in), 1969 (Box 53)
  - Derge, David (Box 53)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 53)
    - Publications: "Modernizing American Government", 1967-1968 (Box 53)
    - Purchase requisition, 1967-1968 (Box 53)
    - Alumni Institute Speech, 1966 (Box 53)
  - Det, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 53)
  - DeValois equipment, 1966-1968 (Box 53)
  - Dil, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 53)
  - Diplomas, 1966-1969 (Box 53)
  - Diploma letters (Box 53)
    - A – F, undated (Box 53)
    - G – M, undated (Box 53)
    - N – Z, undated (Box 53)
    - A – F, undated (Box 53)
    - G – M, undated (Box 53)
    - N – Z, undated (Box 53)
    - A – F, July 1962–June 1963 (Box 53)
    - G – M, July 1962–May 1963 (Box 53)
    - N – Z, July 1962–June 1963 (Box 53)
  - Discrimination, 1967-1968 (Box 53)
  - Discriminatory Practices, Committee on, 1968 (Box 53)
  - Ditchley Foundation, The American, 1966 (Box 53)
  - Do, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 53)
  - Dol, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - Dorson, Richard M., September 1963 (Box 54)
  - Dow, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - Dowling, John C., June 1964–March 1965 (Box 54)
  - Dr, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - Du, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - Dun, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - Dun and Bradstreet, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 54)
  - Duplicating Department, 1966-1968; undated; (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Duplication of courses, 1962-1965 (Box 54)
  - Dur, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - E, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - Earlham College, Richmond, Indiana, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 54)
  - Earlham – I.U. Extension (Box 54)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 54)
    - January – June 1966 (Box 54)
    - Eastern Indiana Center, 1968-1971; (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - 1962-1965, (3 folders) (Box 54)
  - East Africa, University of, 1965 (Box 54)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 54)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 54)
    - Five year report, 1962-1967 (Box 54)
    - Annual report, 1965-1966 (Box 54)
    - Four year report, 1967-1971 (Box 54)
    - Lecture series study program, 1966 (Box 54)
  - Eb, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - Economics (Box 54)
    - 1962 (Box 54)
    - World professorship, 1966-1968 (Box 54)
  - Ed, general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 54)
  - Editorial projects for education, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 54)
  - Education, 1962-1963 (Box 54)
  - Education in World Affairs, 1963-1964; undated; (2 folders) (Box 54)
  - Education in World Affairs (Box 55)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 55)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 55)
  - Education, miscellaneous articles, 1964-1968; (4 folders) (Box 55)
  - Education Abstracts, American College Public Relations Assn. (Box 55)
    - Summer 1965–June 1966 (Box 55)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 55)
    - February–June 1965 (Box 55)
  - Education Commission of the States (Box 55)
    - September 1967–August 1968 (Box 55)
    - August 1966–August 1967 (Box 55)
    - 1967 (Box 55)
    - Compact #3, 1967 (Box 55)
    - Compact # 2, 1966 (Box 55)
    - Compact #1, 1965 (Box 55)
  - Education, School of (Box 55)
    - Report to the National Council for Accreditation, 1963; (3 folders) (Box 55)
    - Report to the National Council for Accreditation, 1963; (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Study of the Space Needs of the School of Education, vol. 1, 1962 (Box 56)
    - Study of the Space Needs of the School of Education, vol. 2, 1962 (Box 56)
    - Annual report, 1961-1962 (Box 56)
    - 1964-1968, (4 folders) (Box 56)
    - Annual report, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 56)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 56)
    - (M.M. Chambers), 1965-1966 (Box 56)
    - Annual report, 1966-1967 (Box 56)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 56)
    - "Development of the Institute of Education and Research, University of the Punjab, Pakistan, 1959-1967: Final report of a project conducted under contractual agreement between Indiana University and the United States Agency for International Development," compiled and edited by Dr. Howard T. Batchelder (Box 56)
    - Programs and plans for discussion, June 1967 (Box 56)
    - Space Committee Report, June 1967 (Box 56)
    - Workshops, 1965-1968 (Box 56)
    - Applicants or candidates for the dean of (Box 56)
      - 1965 (Box 56)
      - David M. Jackson, 1966 (Box 56)
      - Donald J. McCarty, 1965 (Box 56)
      - Gene L. Schwilck, 1966 (Box 56)
      - Richard Turner, undated (Box 56)
      - Roger E. Wilk, 1965 (Box 56)
    - Applicants or candidates – Dean School of Education, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Bureau of Educational Placement Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Box 57)
  - Educational Services Incorporated (Box 57)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 57)
      Note: Includes Articles of Incorporation and Proposed Bylaws
    - 1965-1966 (Box 57)
  - Educational Statistics, 1963-1968 (Box 57)
  - Education, School of – Our Professional Heritage, 1966 (Box 57)
  - Bureau of Educational Studies and Testing, Biennial Report, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - Educational Television Seminar Arlie House – Warrenton, VA, 1963 (Box 57)
  - Educational Television Stations Program Service, 1966 (Box 57)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1962-1967; (5 folders) (Box 57)
  - Education and World Affairs, Incorporated, 1966 (Box 57)
  - Educational Projects, Inc., 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - Edwards, John H. – Fellowships, 1965-1966; undated; (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - Edwards, John – Trust Fund, 1960-1965 (Box 57)
  - Eg general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 57)
  - Eggers and Higgins, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 57)
  - Egypt, 1966-1967 (Box 57)
  - Ei general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 57)
  - Ekanem, Prince Ikot Alfred – Investiture ceremony at I.U., correspondence, 1966-1986 (Box 57)
  - El general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 57)
  - Electronics Department – Annual Report, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - Eli Lilly Co., 1962 (Box 57)
  - Elm general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 57)
  - Elsen, Albert, 1964 (Box 57)
  - Employees, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 57)
  - Employees (Box 58)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Report, 1966 (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 58)
    - Name and Department Listing, 1966-1968 (Box 58)
    - Retired, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 58)
    - Staff Recognition Reception, 1961-1968; (5 folders) (Box 58)
  - Employment Opportunities, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 58)
  - En general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 58)
  - Endowment Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 58)
  - Engineering and Related Undergraduate and Graduate Program in Indianapolis, 1962-1963 (Box 58)
  - Engle, Shirley H., 1960-1967 (Box 58)
  - English, 1962-1963 (Box 58)
  - English Department, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 58)
  - English Language Arts, 1962 (Box 58)
  - English Speaking Union, 1966-1968 (Box 58)
  - Enrollment (Box 58)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 58)
    - Figures – Summer Session, 1962-1963 (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 58)
    - Out-of-State Students, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 59)
    - Prediction (Box 59)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 59)
      - Parkhurst Studies (Box 59)
        - 1955-1966, (2 folders) (Box 59)
        - Hartley, Joseph R., 1964 (Box 59)
    - Regional Campuses, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 59)
    - Statistics, 1961-1968; (6 folders) (Box 59)
  - Environmental Sciences, 1965 (Box 59)
  - Ethnomusicology, 1962-1967 (Box 59)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1968 (Box 59)
  - Equality of Educational Opportunity, University Committee on – I.U. Stillman College relationship, 1964-1968 (Box 59)
  - Equipment – Academic and Administrative, 1967-1968 (Box 59)
  - Equitable Life Assurance Society (Box 60)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 60)
    - Death and Disability Claims, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 60)
  - Er general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 60)
  - Es general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 60)
  - Ethnohistory, Journal of, 1964 (Box 60)
  - Ev general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 60)
  - Evansville, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 60)
  - Evansville College, Evansville, Indiana, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 60)
  - Evansville Study, 1963 (Box 60)
  - Evansville, Univ. of, Evansville, Indiana, 1966-1968 (Box 60)
  - Evening Classes, 1962-1963 (Box 60)
  - Evening Classes and Examinations, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 60)
  - Environment – Center for the Study of the Human Environment (Proposed), 1966 (Box 60)
  - Environmental Studies, 1967 (Box 60)
  - Ewers, Joseph R. (Box 60)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 60)
    - Personal File, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Ewing, Oscar R., Prizes in Philosophy, 1964 (Box 60)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 60)
  - Division of University Extension, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 60)
  - Division of University Extension (Box 61)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 61)
    - Analysis of Income, 1962-1967; (3 folders) (Box 61)
    - Audio-Visual Center, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 61)
    - Audio-Visual Center Net Film Service, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 61)
    - Bureau of Correspondence Study, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - Bureau of Public Discussion, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 61)
    - Bureau of Studies in Adult Education, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 61)
    - Campuses (Box 61)
      - Bloomington, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 61)
      - Calumet Center, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 61)
      - Eastern Campus, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 61)
      - Fort Wayne (Box 61)
        - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 61)
        - 50th Anniversary, 1966-1968 (Box 61)
      - Gary, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 61)
      - Indianapolis (Box 61)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 61)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 61)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 61)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 61)
        - July 1966-December 1967 (Box 61)
        - January-June 1967 (Box 61)
        - July 1967-August 1968 (Box 61)
      - Indiana-Purdue Regional Campus at Fort Wayne, 1964-1966; (2 folders) (Box 61)
      - Indiana-Purdue Southeastern Regional Campus at New Albany and Jeffersonville, 1966-1967 (Box 61)
      - Kokomo, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 61)
      - New Albany Campus, 1966 (Box 62)
      - Northwest Campus, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 62)
      - South Bend, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 62)
      - Southeastern, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 62)
      - South West Center of Indiana and Vincennes University, 1965-1966 (Box 62)
    - Comparative Bookstore Balance Sheets, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 62)
    - Comparative General Financial Report, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 62)
    - Enrollment Summaries, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 62)
    - Regional Campus (Box 62)
      - Capital Appropriations Study, 1965-1975 (Box 62)
      - Coordinating Committee Minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 62)
      - Development (Council of Sate Government's Study), 1965-1966 (Box 62)
      - Directors' Meeting, 1962-1965; (3 folders) (Box 62)
      - Directors' Meeting, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Transfer Students (Study by Anita Lillian Hughes), 1962-1963 (Box 63)
  - Extension Division, 1962-1963; 1966; (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - F general, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 63)
  - Facilities Use (Box 63)
    - 1964-1968, (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Bloomington Metropolitan Schools, 1966 (Box 63)
    - Council of Ten Questionnaire, 1965 (Box 63)
    - Political Use, 1962-1972 (Box 63)
    - Statements of Policy and Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 63)
    - Student Activities Office, 1967-1968 (Box 63)
  - Faculty (Box 63)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 63)
    - Abroad, 1966-1968 (Box 63)
    - Annual Reports, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 63)
    - Appointments, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 63)
    - Appointment Lists (PT-Time), 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 63)
    - Bibliography, 1965-1966 (Box 63)
    - Clippings – Honors, 1964-1965 (Box 63)
    - Clubs – Other Schools (Survey), 1963-1964 (Box 63)
    - Conflict of Interest Problems, 1965-1966 (Box 63)
    - Continuing Committee, 1968 (Box 63)
    - Directory of Faculty with International Interests, 1965 (Box 63)
    - Requests for Information, 1963-1966; (3 folders) (Box 63)
  - Faculty Council (Box 64)
    - 1962-1968, (6 folders) (Box 64)
    - University Counsel File, 1967-1968 (Box 64)
    - Action re Dow Chemical incident, Nov. 9, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Dr. Stahr's address, Nov. 7, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Report of Action, Nov. 9, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Report of the Committee on Academic Freedom, 1965-1966 (Box 64)
    - Elections, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Committees, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 64)
    - Student Affairs Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 64)
    - Committee "Smoke-Ups", March 22, 1966 (Box 64)
    - Agenda and Documents, 1963-1967 (Box 64)
  - Faculty (Box 64)
    - Collective bargaining, undated (Box 64)
    - Course evaluation survey, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 64)
    - Demonstrations, President's House, Nov. 24, 1967 (Box 64)
    - Discussion Group, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 64)
    - Distinguished, University, Research, and Name Professors, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 64)
    - Faculty Emeritus, Retired Faculty and administrative officers, 1961-1968; (7 folders) (Box 64)
    - Form Letters, 1966-1968 (Box 64)
    - Form Letters, 1963-1966; (4 folders) (Box 65)
    - Handbooks, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 65)
    - Histories, 1963-1964; undated (Box 65)
    - Honors (Box 65)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 65)
      - 1963-1964, clippings (Box 65)
    - Leaves of absence, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 65)
    - Lists, new members, etc., 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 65)
    - Lists, Regional campuses, current faculty, undated (Box 65)
    - Lists, new members, etc., 1962-1965; (4 folders) (Box 65)
    - Meeting (Box 65)
      - Whittenberger Auditorium, 1965 (Box 65)
      - Alumni hall, 1966 (Box 65)
    - Newsletter, 1965-1969; (3 folders) (Box 65)
    - Newsletter, 1964-1965 (Box 66)
    - Oaths, legal opinions regarding validity of requiring loyalty statements, 1965 (Box 66)
    - Outside faculty activities and extra compensation policy, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 66)
    - Policy concerning political activities, 1965-1966 (Box 66)
    - Physical Examination Certificates, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 66)
    - Promotions, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 66)
    - Publications, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 66)
    - Reappointments, 1963-1968; (7 folders) (Box 66)
    - Representation allowance, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 66)
    - Retirees, Dinner, 1965-1968; (4 folders) (Box 66)
    - Retirement, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 66)
    - Widows of faculty and administrative officers, 1962 (Box 66)
    - Salaries, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 66)
    - Salaries, 1961-1966; (4 folders) (Box 67)
    - Salaries—Big Ten Schedules, 1961-1966 (Box 67)
    - Salaries—Big Ten Miscellaneous, 1962-1966 (Box 67)
    - Selective Service data, 1966-1968 (Box 67)
    - Staff Identification, 1960-1968; (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Tenure, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Visiting professors, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 67)
    - Work load, 1963-1964 (Box 67)
  - Fam, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 67)
  - Fas, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 67)
  - Fe, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 67)
  - Feasibility study, Indiana University – University of California project, 1966-1968 (Box 67)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 67)
  - Fees, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 67)
  - Fees, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - Fee courtesy report, 1967-1968 (Box 68)
  - Fee remission for children of disabled veterans, 1963 (Box 68)
  - Fellowships, scholarships, and assistantships (Box 68)
    - Announcements, 1968 (Box 68)
    - Danforth, 1966-1968 (Box 68)
    - Fulbright, 1966-1968 (Box 68)
    - Guggenheim, 1966-1968 (Box 68)
    - Announcements, 1965-1966 (Box 68)
    - Danforth, 1965-1966 (Box 68)
    - Fulbright Grants, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 68)
    - Guggenheim, 1966 (Box 68)
    - Edwards, 1965 (Box 68)
    - Announcements, 1964-1965 (Box 68)
    - Danforth, 1965 (Box 68)
    - Fulbright fellowships, 1965 (Box 68)
    - Foreign Area, 1964 (Box 68)
    - Guggenheim, 1964-1965 (Box 68)
    - International Business Machines Corp., 1965 (Box 68)
    - United States Steel Corp., 1964-1965 (Box 68)
    - Announcements, 1964-1965 (Box 68)
    - Danforth, 1963-1964 (Box 68)
    - Guggenheim, 1963-1964 (Box 68)
    - Announcements, 1962-1963 (Box 68)
    - Nato, 1963 (Box 68)
    - Offered by I.U., 1957-1964 (Box 68)
    - Social Sciences Research council, 1964 (Box 68)
    - SEATO (S.E. Asia Treaty Org.), 1960-1963 (Box 68)
    - Woodrow Wilson, 1957-1965 (Box 68)
  - Fen, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 68)
  - Fi, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 68)
  - Fin, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 68)
  - Final Examinations, 1967 (Box 68)
  - Financial report, 1962-1963; (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - Fine Arts Department (Box 68)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 68)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 68)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 68)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 68)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 68)
  - Finney, Donald L., Personnel – Fort Wayne Campus, 1966-1968 (Box 68)
  - Fire Drills, 1948-1967 (Box 68)
  - First National Bank, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - Fis, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 68)
  - Fit, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 68)
  - Fl, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 68)
  - Flight Reports (Box 68)
    - I.U.F. Aircraft, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 68)
  - Flight Reports, undated (Box 69)
  - I.U.F. Aircraft, 1962-1963 (Box 69)
  - Flo, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 69)
  - Florida Atlantic University, 1965 (Box 69)
  - Florida State University, 1964-1965 (Box 69)
  - Fo, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 69)
  - Folklore, 1963-1967; (3 folders) (Box 69)
  - Folklore Institute (Box 69)
    - General, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 69)
    - Annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 69)
    - Archives Annual Report, 1964-1965 (Box 69)
    - National Folk Festival, 1966 (Box 69)
    - Misc. – George H. List; Supplemental research concerning the Cumbiamba, a folk music ensemble of the Atlantic Littoral of Columbia, 1966-1967 (Box 69)
    - Misc. – George H. List; preparation of tape copies of and documentation for the Herskovits Collection of Dahomey and Srinam music and study, 1966 (Box 69)
  - For, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 69)
  - Football (Box 69)
    - 1962 (Box 69)
    - 1962 (Box 69)
      - A-F (Box 69)
      - G-L (Box 69)
      - M-Q (Box 69)
      - R-T (Box 69)
      - U-Z (Box 69)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 69)
      - A-F (Box 69)
      - G-L (Box 69)
      - M-Q (Box 69)
      - R-T (Box 69)
      - U-Z (Box 69)
    - Purdue Game, 1963 (Box 69)
    - Tickets, 1963-1964 (Box 69)
    - Tickets, complimentary, 1963 (Box 69)
    - 1963, (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - Misc., 1962-1963 (Box 69)
    - Purdue Game (Box 69)
      - 1962 (Box 69)
      - 1964 (Box 69)
    - Tickets, 1962-1963 (Box 69)
    - Tickets, complimentary (Box 69)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 69)
      - 1964-1965 (Box 69)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 69)
      - A-F (Box 69)
      - G-L (Box 69)
      - M-Q (Box 69)
      - R-T (Box 69)
      - U-Z (Box 69)
    - Tickets, 1964-1965 (Box 69)
  - Ford Foundation, 1963-1965; (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Economics program at Andres Bello (university), Caracas, Venezuela; Latin American program possibilities, 1965 (Box 70)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 70)
    - January – August 1968 (Box 70)
    - July – December 1967 (Box 70)
    - International Affairs Center, grant report, 1967 (Box 70)
    - July 1966 – June 1967 (Box 70)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 70)
    - Application for support of programs of international affairs center, 1965-1966 (Box 70)
    - Annual report (Box 70)
    - Computer (math model) proposed for I.U. and Franklin College, 1966 (Box 70)
    - Indiana University Program (support for improving foreign lang. teaching), 1965-1966 (Box 70)
    - Proposal to assist educational institutions in Indonesia, 1964 (Box 70)
    - Research grants, 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Educational aid program, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 70)
    - Scholarship board, 1962-1964 (Box 70)
  - Foreign area fellowship program (Sutton), 1962 (Box 70)
  - Foreign students (Box 70)
    - October 1967 – August 1968 (Box 70)
    - July 1966 – September 1967 (Box 70)
  - Foreign students, 1963-1966; (4 folders) (Box 71)
  - Foreign study centers (Box 71)
    - Venice (proposed), 1966-1968 (Box 71)
    - 1965-1968, (2 folders) (Box 71)
    - University of the Americas (Mexico), 1966 (Box 71)
    - University of Bologna (Italy), 1965 (Box 71)
    - I.U. Center for scholarly research in London (proposed), 1966 (Box 71)
    - International university at Nice (proposed), 1964-1966 (Box 71)
    - University of San Marco (Peru), 1967 (Box 71)
    - 1963-1965, (2 folders) (Box 71)
  - Foreign visiting professors, 1963-1965; (3 folders) (Box 71)
  - Foreign visitors (Box 71)
    - May 1967 – August 1968 (Box 71)
    - July 1966 – April 1967 (Box 71)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Ishaya Audu (Ahmed Bello University, Zaria, Nigeria), 1966-1968 (Box 71)
    - Vasco Leitao DeCunha, Ambassador from Brazil, 1966-1968 (Box 71)
    - Princess Irene of Greece, 1966-1968 (Box 71)
    - Pres. K. Sejima (Osaka Sangyo University), 1966-1968 (Box 71)
    - Dr. Lujo Toncic-Sorinji, Austrian foreign minister, 1966-1968 (Box 71)
    - Prince Dhani and Princess Sibpan, 1966-1968 (Box 71)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 71)
    - Dignitaries invited to international exhibit dinner (November 6-7, 1966), [1965] (Box 71)
    - Representatives of science council of Japan, May 19-22, 1966 (Box 71)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Akimasa Mitsuta (UNESCO), 1966 (Box 71)
    - Myshkov, Anatoly G., 1965 (Box 71)
    - Claudio G. de Souza, 1965 (Box 71)
    - Yugoslav, 1965 (Box 71)
    - 1965 (Box 71)
    - Mr. Cesare Gnoli, 1965 (Box 71)
    - International week at I.U., November 10-15, 1964 (Box 71)
    - Sholl, Reginald R., 1964 (Box 71)
    - Ambassador J.K. Waller of Australia, 1965 (Box 71)
    - 1964 (Box 71)
    - Annan, Noel, 1964 (Box 71)
    - Buchana, Atthakor, 1964 (Box 71)
    - Burkchardt, Lukas, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Kreisky, Bruno, 1963-1964 (Box 71)
    - General Mamet Tanumidjaja, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Paz Estenssoro, Victor (president of Bolivia), 1963 (Box 71)
    - Ramasinaiva, Jean, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Sarguini, Mohamed, 1963 (Box 71)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 71)
    - Bulgarian diplomats, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Edhem Camo, 1962 (Box 71)
    - Ruy Esteves de Azeredo, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Evgeni J. Evtushenko, 1962-1963 (Box 71)
    - Zafrulla Khan, 1963 (Box 71)
    - M.L. Pun Malakul, 1962-1963 (Box 71)
    - Oumar Sow, 1962 (Box 71)
    - Tashkent University Delegation, 1962 (Box 71)
  - Fort Wayne Fine Arts Foundation, 1965 (Box 71)